Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Anarchism Serials TAM.766
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Anarchism Serials
1890-2010
1960-1999
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Federazione anarchica italiana
TAM.766
19 Linear Feet in 24 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 33 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Anarchism Serials contains over 300 titles on anarchist movements and philosophies in the United States, Italy, Spain, France, and other countries. The collection dates between 1890 and 2010, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through 1990s. Topics include anarchist theories and principles regarding economic, political, social, and labor issues in the United States and other countries; anarcho-syndicalist movements in Europe in the 20th century; and feminist movements within anarchist organizations.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to anarchism drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Anarchism Serials contains over 300 titles on anarchist movements and philosophies in the United States (US), Italy, Spain, France, and other countries. The collection dates between 1890 and 2010, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through 1990s. Topics include anarchist theories and principles regarding economic, political, social, and labor issues in Europe, the US, and other countries; anarcho-syndicalist movements in Europe in the 20th century; and feminist movements within anarchist organizations. Large runs of titles include Umanità Nova, Freedom: Anarchist Weekly, Direkte Aktion, Orto: Revista Cultural de Ideas Acratas, and A Rivista Anarchica. The collection includes serials published in the US, Europe, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, Africa, and Asia, with the majority of the titles published in France, Italy, Spain, and the United Kingdom (UK). Anarchist organizations represented in the collection include national federations such as the Italian Anarchist Federation (Federazione Anarchica Italiana) and Germany's Free Workers' Union (Freie Arbeiterinnen- und Arbeiter-Union), publishing houses such as London's Freedom Press, and state and local-level groups.
Anarchism -- Periodicals.; Anarchism -- Spain.; Anarchism -- Italy.; Anarchism -- England.; Women and anarchism.; Freie Arbeiterinnen- und Arbeiter-Union; Freedom Press (London, England)
- @-Wire: Autonomous Anarchist Action, New York, NY, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A Distribution: A Distribution, Brooklyn, NY, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Gallery: n.p., Athens, Greece, circa 1980s (Box 53, Folder 1)
- A Mayor: Latin American Anarchist Black Cross, Miami, FL, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A New World Rising: A New World Rising, Providence, RI, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- A Rivista Anarchica: Editrice A, Milan, Italy, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5-8, Box 2, Folder 1-5, Box 3, Box 4, Folder 1-3, Box 28, Folder 1-2)
- A-infos from Germany: Anarchist Black Cross, Germany, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- A-infos from Greece: Anarchist Black Cross, Athens, Greece, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- A-Infos Information Bulletin: Anarchist Black Cross, Stockholm, Sweden, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- A-Kontra: Ceskoslovenskeho Anarchistickeho Sdruzeni, Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7, Box 28, Folder 3)
- a-zine: Warsaw, Poland, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- AA Nachrichten: AA, Burgenland, Austria, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- AANN Bulletin: Anti-Authoritarian News Network, Toronto, Ontario, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Abatalha: Confederacao do Trabalho, Lisbon, Portugal, 1975-1982 (Box 24, Folder 1-2, Box 28, Folder 4-6)
- Abolishing the Borders from Below: Abolishing BB, Berlin, Germany, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Acção directa: revista anarquista: Associacao de Grupos Autonomos Anaquistas, Lisbon, Portugal, 1946, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12, Box 24, Folder 3)
- Accion Libertaria: La Regional de Asturias y Leon CNT-AIT, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Active Transformation: Students for Environmental Action, East Lansing, MI, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Acuerdos Pleno Nacional Anarquista: Comision Pro Federacion Libertaria del Uruguay, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Against the Grain: Against the Grain Collective, New York, NY, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Agora: Agora, Toulouse, France, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Albor: Hoja Anarquista: Vitoria, Spain, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Alpha: Gia Tēn Koinōnikē Apeleutherōse: Ekdotēs "Alpha" A.M.K., Athens, Greece, 1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 11)
- Alternativa Libertaria: Foglio Telematico della Federazione dei Comunisti Anarchici: Federazione dei Comunisti Anarchici, Fano, Italy, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Alternative Libertaire: International Libertarian Solidarity, Paris, France, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 4-7, Box 6, Folder 1-2, Box 23, Folder 4, Box 28, Folder 11)
- Anarcha Feminist Notes, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Anarchismo: Italy, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Anarchist: Anarchist Coil, Athens, Greece, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Anarchist Age Monthly Review: Libertarian Workers for a Self Managed Society, Parkville, Victoria, Australia, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Anarchist Age Weekly Review: Libertarian Workers for a Self Managed Society, Parkville, Victoria, Australia, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Anarchist Black Cross Bulletin: CABC, Chicago, IL, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Anarchist Black Cross Bulletin: London Anarchist Black Cross, London, UK, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Anarchist Black Cross Discussion Bulletin: NYAYF, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Anarchist Black Cross Fedration Update: ABDF Update, Paterson, NJ, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Anarchist Black Dragon: Washington State Penitentiary/Anarchist Black Dragon Collective, Walla Walla, WA, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Anarchist Catalog: Libertarian Book Club, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Anarchist Feminist Notes: Tiamat, Ithaca, NY, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Anarchist Labor Bulletin: Anarchist Labor Network, San Francisco, CA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Anarchist Panther: Anarchist Panther, Brooklyn, NY, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Anarchistisches Mitteilungsblatt, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Anarchy Los Angeles: Kimtex Corporation, Los Angeles, CA, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Anarchy: A Journal of Anarchist Ideas: Express Printers, London, UK, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Anarkiviu: Arkiviu "T. Serra", Guasila, Italy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Anti-State Documentation & News Network (ASDNN): Anarchist Black Cross, London, UK, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- April: Anarkopress Ekonomisk Forening, Stockholm, Sweden, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Arbeider Solidaritet: Norsk Syndikalistisk Forbund, Oslo, Norway, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Arcipelago: Gruppo Emma Goldman, Torino, Italy, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- As We See It!: Columbia Anarchist League, Columbia, MO, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Ateneu: Opusculo Mensal Anarquista: Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Atlantic Anarchist Circle: Atlantic Anarchist Circle, New York, NY, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Anarchist Circle Newsletter: Atlantic Anarchist Circle, Philadelphia, PA, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Arbayter Fraynd (The Workers Friend): Workers Friend Group, London, England, 1908 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- August Spies: Sioux Falls, SD, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Australian Anarchist Centenary Celebrations: A.A.C.C.C., Melborne, Australia, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Autogestion: CNT Trabajadores de Telefonica AIT, Spain, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Autogestione: Rome, Italy, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Autonomia: Mexico, D.F., 2003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Autonomy: Autonomy News Service, Toronto, Ontario, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Azione Diretta: Zurich, Switzerland, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Barricada: Barricada Collective, Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bayou La Rose: New Orleans, LA, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Bayou La Rose: Huntsville, AR, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Bayou La Rose: Survival Network Information Center, Tacoma, WA, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Bicicleta: Revista de Comunicaciones Libertarias: Bicicleta, Madrid, Spain, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Big Apple Libertarian: New York City Libertarian Party, New York, NY, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Black & Red Outlook: Anarchist Syndicalist Alliance, Manchester, UK, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Black and Blue: Anarchist Black Cross, Collingwood, Australia, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Black and Red: Anarchist Caucus, CoC, Brooklyn, NY, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Black Fist: Black Fist Collective, Houston, TX, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23, Box 29, Folder 5)
- Black Sheep: Black Sheep, Swansea, UK, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Black Star: Black Star, Wisconsin, WI, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Black Star: Black Star, Flagstaff, AZ, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Blast!: Agitator Index Collective, Minneapolis, MN, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Boicot: CNT Fed. Local-Madrid, Madrid, Spain, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Boletim de Informacao Anarquista: Centro de Cultura Libertaria, Almada, Portugal, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Boletin de Construccion: Sindicato Unico de la Construccion de Barcelona CNT-AIT, Barcelona, Spain, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Boletin de Informacion: Confederacion Nacional del Trabajo y la Federacion Anarquista Iberica, Barcelona, Spain, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Boletin de la Comision Pro-Congreso Internacional: Comisión de Relaciones Internacionales Anarquistas, Paris, France, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Boletin Informativo de los 32 Gremios Democraticos: Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Bolletino Interno: Unione Sindicale Italiana, Palermo, Italy, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Bolton Anarchist: Bolton, UK, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Bound Together Newsletter: Bound Together Anarchist Collective, San Francisco, CA, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Brigada Subversiva: Mexico City, Mexico, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- British Columbia Blackout: Autonomy News Service, Vancouver, BC, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Bulldozer: International Anarchist Black Cross, Germany, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Bulletin - Centre International de Recherches sur l'Anarchisme: Centre International de Recherches sur l'Anarchisme, Geneva, Switzerland, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 25, Box 29, Folder 5)
- Canaan Newsletter: Kolokol Publications, Brussels, Belgium, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Catalogo del Fondo Bibliografio: Fundacion de Estudios Libertarios Anselmo Lorenzo, Madrid, Spain, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Catamount Tavern News: Green Mountain Anarchist Collective, Montpelier, VT, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Centre International de Recherches sur l'Anarchisme Bulletin: Centre International De Recherches Sur l'Anarchisme, Paris, France, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Certamen Internacional: La Protesta, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- CFDT Syndicalisme: Confédération Française Démocratique du Travail, Paris, France, 1981-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1-6, Box 31, Folder 1-9, Box 32, Folder 1-4)
- Chain Reaction: Chain Reaction Collective/Austin ABC Publisher/Distributor, Homewood, IL/Austin, TX, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Challenge: Challenge Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Chaotic World News and Olds: TESC, Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Classes en Lutte...: Bulletin National de la Federation des Travailleurs de l'Education (CNT): Federation des Travailleurs de l'Education (CNT), Paris, France, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Clone: Hunter College, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Collana "La Rivolta": Opuscolletti di Propaganda Rivoluzionaria e Anarchica: Editrice "La Fiaccola", Ragusa, Italy, 1966-1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Comment: NYU's Journal of Political Ideas: NYU Libertarian Studies Association, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- commonweal: Revolutionary Journal of Anarchist-Communism, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- comunitas, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- contraFLOW: European Counter Network (ECN), London, UK, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23, Box 29, Folder 13)
- Controborghese: Frosinone, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Correa: Colective Anarquista, Venezuela, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 24, Box 23, Folder 6)
- Counter Information: Counter Information, Glasgow, Scotland, 1986-1994 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 29, Folder 14)
- Cuadernos para una Enciclopedia Histórica del Anarquismo Español: Edita AIP, Vitoria, Spain, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cultura Libertaria: Asociacion Isaac Puente, Vitoria, Spain, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3, Box 1, Folder 1)
- De Nar:, Brussels, Belgium, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Debattre: Alternative Libertaire, Paris, France, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Debout Postiers: Journal des syndicalistes Proletariens, Undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Defiance: Newscastle Anarchists Newsletter: Anarcho-Syndicalist Federation/Newcastle Anarcho-Artists Greater Building Society, Hamilton, Australia, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Demanarchie: Montreal, Quebec, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Demolition Derby: Demolition Derby, Montreal, Quebec, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5, Box 29, Folder 18)
- Desde Abajo: Mexico City, Mexico, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Die Direkte Aktion: Syndikalistischen Anarchismus, Berlin, Germany, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Die Internationale: Deutschen Anarchosyndikalisten, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dielo Truda-Probuzhdenie: New York, NY, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Directe Actie: Anarchistische Groep Amsterdam, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Direkte Aktion: Anarko-Syndikalistisk Organisation, Copenhagen, Sweden, 1993-2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Direkte Aktion: Direkte Aktion, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1989-1995 (Box 9, Folder 14, Box 29, Folder 15-16)
- Direkte Aktion: Freien ArbeiterInnen-Union IAA, Hamburg, Germany, 1980-2010 (Box 9, Folder 13, Folder 15, Box 10, Folder 1-5, Box 24, Folder 6-12, Box 25, Folder 1-6, Box 26, Folder 1-4, Box 29, Folder 17)
- Direkte Aktion: Kulturföreningen Direkte Aktion, Stockholm, Sweden, 1997-2007 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Discussion: A Journal for Free Spirits: Laurance Labadie, Detroit, MI, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Dossier Contri Buti al Dibattito e Partecipanti: Centro Studi Libertari, Milan, Italy, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Dott Leete: Umanita Nova, Spezzano Albanese, Italy, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Echomedia: London Echomedia, London, UK, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Ecomedia Bulletin: Ecomedia, Toronto, Ontario, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9, Box 29, Folder 19)
- Ecomedia Seattle: Seattle, WA, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10, Box 29, Folder 20)
- Ekintza Zuzena: Revista Libertaria: Ediciones EZ Argitaraldiak, Bilbao, Spain, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ekomedia Bulletin-Toronto: Anti-Authoritarian News Network, Toronto, Ontario, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- El Acratador: Zaragoza, Spain, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- El Baifo: S/C de Tenerife, Islas Canarias.: Tenerife, Canary Islands, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- El Compita: El Compita, Mexico, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- El Libertario: Federacion Libertaria Argentina (FLA) Adherida a la Internacional de Federaciones Anaquistas (IFA), Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3, Box 29, Folder 24)
- El Productor: Cuba, 1901 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- El Solidario: Revista de la Confederación Sindical Solidaridad Obrera: Confederacion Sindical Solidaridad Obrera, Madrid, Spain, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- El Unico: Publicación Periódica del Pensamiento Individualista: Pensamiento Individualista, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Encuentros: Ateno Ibertario Pueblo-Seco, Barcelona, Spain, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Entente Anarchiste: Paris, France, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Espana Libre: Sociedades Hispanas Confederadas de Los Estados Unidos de America, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- EПI TA ПPOΣΩ: EΣE, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Exegerse: Syspeirōsē Anarchikōn, Athens, Greece, 1990-1991 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 12)
- Fighting for Our Lives: An Anarchist Primer: Crimeth Inc., Salem, OR, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- For Anarchist Agitators: Social Revolutionary Anarchist Federation, Mountain View, CA, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Free Association Newsletter: Free Association, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Free Society: Free Society, Minneapolis, MN, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Free Society Library: Free Society Library, San Francisco, CA, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 12, Box 53, Folder 2)
- Freedom: Road to Freedom Publishing Association, New York, NY, 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 25-26)
- Freedom Press Bookshop: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Freedom: Anarchist Fortnightly: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1978-2005 (Box 11, Folder 14-16, Box 29, Folder 27, Box Shared Tamiment 063, Folder 14-15)
- Freedom: Anarchist Pamphlets: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Freedom: Anarchist Weekly: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1964-1976 (Box 32, Folder 5-12, Box 33, Folder 1-5, Box 34, Folder 1-6, Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- Freedom's Anarchist Review: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Freespace: SRAF, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Freespace Newsletter: SRAF, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Freie Presse: Freiheitlich-Sozialistisches Magazin: An-Archia Verlag, Wetzlar, Germany, Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Front Ouvrier: Organe d'Information et de Discussion Syndicales, Paris, France, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Gay Anarchist: Libertarian-Socialist Gay Caucus, Hollywood, CA, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Germinal: Mensuel de Desintoxication Sociale: Groupe Anarchiste D'Amiens (F.A.), Amiens, France, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Guangara Libertaria: International Society for Historical and Social Studies, Inc., Miami, FL, 1980-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
- Hachi Roku Hiroshima: Museifushugisha Zenkokushukai Hokokusho, Osaka, Japan, 1986 (Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 3)
- Harbinger: Crimeth Inc., Atlanta, GA/Olympia, WA, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1, Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 8)
- Haymarket: Haymarket, Inc., Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Haymarket News: Heymarket People's Fund, Boston, MA, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Here and Now: Here & Now, Glasgow, Scotland, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Here and Now: West Yorkshire Collective, Leeds, UK, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Hiedra Negra: Madrid, Spain, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Hiroshima Museifu Shinpo: Hiroshima Museifushugi Kenkyukai (Hiroshima Anarchy News), 1986 (Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 2)
- Hooly-Kopsin: Freedom Hill Pressery, Burbank, CA, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- i-D Magazine: i-D magazine, London, UK, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Ideas & Action: Workers Solidarity Alliance, San Francisco, CA, 1982-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8, Box 35, Folder 6-7)
- iiLibertad: C.A.S.P.A. y de los Presos Anarquistas, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Il Libertario: Milan, Italy, 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 11)
- Il Peccato 13: Umanita Nova, Italy, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
- Il Risveglio Anarchico, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
- il rovescio: Il Rovescio, Imola, Italy, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Il Volantone: Officina dell'Autogestione/AIT, Italy, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Impact Press: IMPACT Press, Orlando, FL, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- In The Trenches...: Ali Khalid Abdullh, Freeland, MI, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Incendiary Devices: Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Individuo nella Società: Italy, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Infinite Onion: Infinite Onion, Colorado Springs, CO, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Iniziativa Anarchica: Iniziativa Anarchica, Pisa, Italy, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Instead of a Magazine: Instead of a Magazine, Willimantic, CT, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Intermundo: Biblioteca/Archivo "Alberto Ghiraldo", Montevideo, Uruguay, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- International Anarchist Press Syndicate Bulletin: International Anarchist Press Syndicate, New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Itaca: Vila-real, Spain, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- IZTOK: France, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2, Box 53, Folder 4)
- Jake Libertario: Federacion Iberica De Juventudes Libertarias, Valencia, Spain, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Japanese Anarchy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Jeunes Libertaires, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Job+: Le Dossier: Section Universitaire, Toulouse, France, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Journal of Anarchy & Black Revolution: Lorenzo Komboa Ervin, Chattanooga, TN, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Kronstadt Rebellion: Der Syndikalist, Berlin, Germany, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- L'Adunata dei Refrattari: Constantino Zonchello, New York, NY, 1949-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1-5, Box 37, Folder 1-8)
- L'Agitazione del Sud: L'Agitazione del Sud, Palermo, Italy, 1957-1968 (Box 26, Folder 10-11, Box 27)
- l'anarcho-syndicalisme et l'anarchisme: rapport de Pierre Besnard: Monde Libertaire, Paris, France, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- L'Assemblea: Unione Sindicale Italiana, Ancona, Italy, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- L'Avvenire Libertario: Milan, Italy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
- L'Azione Libertaria: Sicily, Italy, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- L'Enrage: L'Enrage, Paris, France, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- L'Internazionale: L'Internazionale, Forli, Italy, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 14, Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 10)
- L'Unite Syndicale: Paris, France, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- La Federacion: Grupaciones Anarquistas, Manlleu, Spain, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- La Federation Syndicale Mondiale salue le XIe Festival Mondial de la Jeunesse et des Etudiants: La Federation Syndicale Mondiale, Prague, Czechoslovakia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
- La Feuille Anarchiste: Hommes Libres, Paris, France, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- La Feuille d'Infos du Cira: Centre International de Recherches sur l'Anarchisme, Marseille, France, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- La Gazeta: Organo de Difusion de las Ideas Anarquistas: Colectivo Anarquista, Caracas, Venezuela, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- La Libertad: Agrupaciones Anarquistas, Barcelona, Spain, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- La Nigra Flago: Anarkista Federacio Japana, Japan, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- La Protesta: Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1928, 1955-1962 (Box 14, Folder 18, Box 38, Folder 2, Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 9, Box 54, Folder 6)
- La Puca i el General, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- La Sociale: Paris, France, 1895-1896 (Box 52)
- La Vie de la Recherche Scientifique: Syndicat National des Chercheurs Scientifiques, Paris, France, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- La Voix Du Travailleur Algerien: Federation de France de l'Union des Syndicats des Travailleurs Algeriens, Paris, France, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- le cri de revolte, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Le Monde Libertaire: Organ de la Federation Anarchiste, Paris, France, 1956-2002 (Box 14, Folder 21, Box 15, Folder 1-6, Box 38, Folder 3-14)
- Le Père Peinard: Paris, France, 1891-1893 (Box 52)
- Le Refractaire: May Picqueray, Paris, France, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)